{
  "meta": {
    "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
    "perDifficulty": 20,
    "createdAt": "2026-01-17T09:57:32.275375"
  },
  "problems": {
    "1": [
      {
        "id": "P0326398553809242",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "18+(10)-(-2) = ?",
        "answer": "30",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P0711797601534792",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "-2+(-2)-(9) = ?",
        "answer": "-13",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P5897895892052578",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "-6+(-4)-(20) = ?",
        "answer": "-30",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P5445623787105787",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "-8+(7)-(-13) = ?",
        "answer": "12",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P0714098368558141",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "-11+(-3)-(-11) = ?",
        "answer": "-3",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P7489577220696233",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "-10+(-1)-(18) = ?",
        "answer": "-29",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P1243536581747082",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "16+(-2)-(8) = ?",
        "answer": "6",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P5004721771179256",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "-1+(5)-(-3) = ?",
        "answer": "7",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P5980366620411036",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "11+(8)-(-15) = ?",
        "answer": "34",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P2503679024120039",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "7+(0)-(18) = ?",
        "answer": "-11",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P5871229317097834",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "-15+(-6)-(16) = ?",
        "answer": "-37",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P0402316731446161",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "-19+(-3)-(16) = ?",
        "answer": "-38",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P6515094894336864",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "-9+(10)-(13) = ?",
        "answer": "-12",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P4358849870770030",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "-3+(-9)-(17) = ?",
        "answer": "-29",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P3479610562946504",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "11+(-15)-(10) = ?",
        "answer": "-14",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P8577330944003526",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "1+(0)-(-14) = ?",
        "answer": "15",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P2882177953614557",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "1+(6)-(11) = ?",
        "answer": "-4",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P4548259086017294",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "5+(15)-(-18) = ?",
        "answer": "38",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P1159216014309578",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "0+(-4)-(0) = ?",
        "answer": "-4",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P6576603864831290",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "5+(12)-(-20) = ?",
        "answer": "37",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      }
    ],
    "2": [
      {
        "id": "P4132475707993215",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "1.9×(0.9) = ?",
        "answer": "1.71",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P3617793591516752",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "-2.6×(1.6) = ?",
        "answer": "-4.16",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P6254087421450090",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "4.6×(1.3) = ?",
        "answer": "5.98",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P2035582383502738",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "4.7×(-4.4) = ?",
        "answer": "-20.68",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P9276727608444478",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "2.0×(-3.4) = ?",
        "answer": "-6.8",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P4847117969499981",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "0.6×(3.9) = ?",
        "answer": "2.34",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P6088716670819649",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "-4.7×(3.0) = ?",
        "answer": "-14.1",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P1583781638052324",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "-2.0×(4.0) = ?",
        "answer": "-8.0",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P5522514090537330",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "2.0×(-4.9) = ?",
        "answer": "-9.8",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P9922571393952196",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "-3.9×(-2.2) = ?",
        "answer": "8.58",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P9470607423593562",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "-3.6×(0.9) = ?",
        "answer": "-3.24",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P4983755047071953",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "3.2×(-3.1) = ?",
        "answer": "-9.92",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P5088720150695117",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "4.1×(-1.3) = ?",
        "answer": "-5.33",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P8347239455766944",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "-1.6×(0.3) = ?",
        "answer": "-0.48",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P4567864727323135",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "1.0×(-1.9) = ?",
        "answer": "-1.9",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P1906103709479283",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "-3.2×(-0.1) = ?",
        "answer": "0.32",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P7462925454923977",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "2.6×(1.5) = ?",
        "answer": "3.9",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P2762474028220409",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "-3.3×(-4.2) = ?",
        "answer": "13.86",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P9342483936825202",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "0.3×(-0.7) = ?",
        "answer": "-0.21",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P8205494731855784",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "1.4×(-1.6) = ?",
        "answer": "-2.24",
        "answerType": "number",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      }
    ],
    "3": [
      {
        "id": "P9989023332293388",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "question": "(0/4) ÷ (9/6) = ? (기약분수)",
        "answer": "0",
        "answerType": "string",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P4843413855517203",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "question": "(6/3) ÷ (5/6) = ? (기약분수)",
        "answer": "12/5",
        "answerType": "string",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P4553446168665011",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "question": "(1/6) ÷ (8/5) = ? (기약분수)",
        "answer": "5/48",
        "answerType": "string",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P3829708489296022",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "question": "(1/3) ÷ (-2/6) = ? (기약분수)",
        "answer": "-1",
        "answerType": "string",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P7052278810250026",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "question": "(4/2) ÷ (1/5) = ? (기약분수)",
        "answer": "10",
        "answerType": "string",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P9648244383709104",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "question": "(3/5) ÷ (-5/5) = ? (기약분수)",
        "answer": "-3/5",
        "answerType": "string",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P8697003133622154",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "question": "(-5/6) ÷ (9/4) = ? (기약분수)",
        "answer": "-10/27",
        "answerType": "string",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P0153475979152606",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "question": "(5/2) ÷ (7/5) = ? (기약분수)",
        "answer": "25/14",
        "answerType": "string",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P4694906009847319",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "question": "(-5/5) ÷ (-5/2) = ? (기약분수)",
        "answer": "2/5",
        "answerType": "string",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P8517652923506914",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "question": "(-1/4) ÷ (3/2) = ? (기약분수)",
        "answer": "-1/6",
        "answerType": "string",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P8723830173985363",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "question": "(8/5) ÷ (1/5) = ? (기약분수)",
        "answer": "8",
        "answerType": "string",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P6311610168546405",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "question": "(-8/6) ÷ (-7/3) = ? (기약분수)",
        "answer": "4/7",
        "answerType": "string",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P9783377282205456",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "question": "(0/3) ÷ (-7/5) = ? (기약분수)",
        "answer": "0",
        "answerType": "string",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P9034240620504860",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "question": "(-6/5) ÷ (-4/4) = ? (기약분수)",
        "answer": "6/5",
        "answerType": "string",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P3584633423003634",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "question": "(-8/4) ÷ (-8/4) = ? (기약분수)",
        "answer": "1",
        "answerType": "string",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P4120517489755754",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "question": "(4/3) ÷ (-2/6) = ? (기약분수)",
        "answer": "-4",
        "answerType": "string",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P6094917868885368",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "question": "(-4/3) ÷ (-4/2) = ? (기약분수)",
        "answer": "2/3",
        "answerType": "string",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P9128290160235548",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "question": "(3/6) ÷ (-2/5) = ? (기약분수)",
        "answer": "-5/4",
        "answerType": "string",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P4595704991767310",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "question": "(-5/3) ÷ (5/4) = ? (기약분수)",
        "answer": "-4/3",
        "answerType": "string",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      },
      {
        "id": "P1579756220717869",
        "unitId": "m1-1-1-II-2",
        "difficulty": 3,
        "question": "(-9/5) ÷ (1/6) = ? (기약분수)",
        "answer": "-54/5",
        "answerType": "string",
        "tolerance": 0,
        "unitLabel": "",
        "hint": "",
        "explain": "",
        "tags": []
      }
    ]
  }
}